{
  "admin": [
    {
      "admin_name": "admin",
      "admin_password": "1234"
    }
  ],
  "subject": [
    {
      "subject_name": "Maths",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "subject_name": "English",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "subject_name": "Science",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "Exam": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "exam_desc": "This is Math Exam",
      "exam_date": "17-9-2021 17:49:39",
      "exam_marks": "5",
      "exam_totalQuestion": "5",
      "exam_passMarks": "3",
      "exam_level": "Easy"
    },
    {
      "exam_name": "Physics",
      "exam_desc": "learning of thermodynamics",
      "exam_level": "5",
      "exam_passMarks": "25",
      "exam_totalQuestion": "5",
      "exam_marks": "50",
      "exam_date": "6-12-2023 10:20:8",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "exam_name": "Software Engineer role",
      "exam_desc": "Answer all the questions without fail",
      "exam_level": "Medium",
      "exam_passMarks": "15",
      "exam_totalQuestion": "3",
      "exam_marks": "30",
      "exam_date": "6-12-2023 14:41:22",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 12
    }
  ],
  "Question": [
    {
      "question_name": "what is thermodynamics?",
      "option_one": "fission",
      "option_two": "fussion",
      "option_three": "absorption",
      "option_four": "adsorption",
      "question_answer": "fission",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is thermodynamics?",
      "option_one": "fission",
      "option_two": "fussion",
      "option_three": "absorption",
      "option_four": "adsorption",
      "question_answer": "fission",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is thermodynamics?",
      "option_one": "fission",
      "option_two": "fussion",
      "option_three": "absorption",
      "option_four": "adsorption",
      "question_answer": "fission",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is java?",
      "option_one": "mvc",
      "option_two": "oops",
      "option_three": "platform independent",
      "option_four": "wora",
      "question_answer": "wora",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is javascript?",
      "option_one": "scripting language",
      "option_two": "typescript",
      "option_three": "naren",
      "option_four": "javad",
      "question_answer": "naren",
      "exam_id": "2",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is java?",
      "option_one": "oops",
      "option_two": "owra",
      "option_three": "platform independent",
      "option_four": "none of these above",
      "question_answer": "owra",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is oops?",
      "option_one": "object orientedprogramming language",
      "option_two": "object oracle programming language",
      "option_three": "object oriented programming structure",
      "option_four": "object oriented protractor structure",
      "question_answer": "object oriented programming structure",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is interface?",
      "option_one": "To define roles",
      "option_two": "To define kind",
      "option_three": "To define object",
      "option_four": "To define relation",
      "question_answer": "To define roles",
      "exam_id": ":id",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is abstract?",
      "option_one": "kind of",
      "option_two": "role of",
      "option_three": "call of",
      "option_four": "soul of",
      "question_answer": "kind of",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "question_name": "what is exception?",
      "option_one": "event",
      "option_two": "mild error",
      "option_three": "service",
      "option_four": "not error",
      "question_answer": "mild error",
      "exam_id": "3",
      "subject_name": "java",
      "id": 15
    }
  ],
  "Result": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": "3",
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "12-23-12",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": "3",
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "12-23-12",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": "3",
      "user_email": "shiv@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "12-23-12",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5"
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 3,
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "18-9-2021 20:49:39",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": "vishnu@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "19-9-2021 15:11:27",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": "agni@gmail.com",
      "exam_date": "19-9-2021 15:20:37",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 5,
      "user_email": null,
      "exam_date": "6-12-2023 18:23:18",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 3,
      "user_email": null,
      "exam_date": "6-12-2023 18:23:41",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Pass",
      "result_score": 4,
      "user_email": null,
      "exam_date": "6-12-2023 18:27:38",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "result_status": "Fail",
      "result_score": 0,
      "user_email": null,
      "exam_date": "7-12-2023 9:59:50",
      "exam_name": "Maths",
      "total_marks": "5",
      "exam_id": "1",
      "total_Question": "5",
      "id": 10
    }
  ],
  "user": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "user_name": "ram",
      "user_email": "ram@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "1234"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "user_name": "shiv",
      "user_email": "shiv@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "1234"
    },
    {
      "user_name": "Vishnu",
      "user_email": "vishnu@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "123",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "user_name": "Agni",
      "user_email": "agni@gmail.com",
      "user_password": "123",
      "id": 4
    }
  ]
}